A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Indo-US Subcommission on Education and Culture, RG 3 FA1401
Rockefeller Archive Center
Asian Cultural Council records, Indo-US Subcommission on Education and Culture, RG 3
1971-1996
Rockefeller Archive Center
Asian Cultural Council
FA1401
15.94 Cubic Feet 38 document boxes, 1 half-document box and 1 standard record storage box.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Arrangement
Record Group 2 is arranged in five series:
Series 1: General Files
Series 2: Grants
Series 3: Festival of India (FOI)
Series 4: Museum Exchange
Series 5: Video
Biographical / Historical
The Asian Cultural Council is a publicly supported not for profit 501(c)(3) established in 1980 to support cultural exchange between Asia and the United States. The Council carries forward the mission of the Asian Cultural Program of the JDR 3rd Fund, which had been created by JDR 3rd in 1963 and was officially dissolved in July 1979.
The Asian Cultural Council maintains offices in New York, Hong Kong, Manila (Philippines), Taipei (Taiwan) and Tokyo. ACC affiliation with the Rockefeller Brothers Fund began in 1991, enabling the Council to reduce administrative overhead and devote a larger percentage of its funds directly to grants and program development.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Asian Cultural Council records were donated to the RAC in 2010.
Other Finding Aids
Other available findig aids describing the Asian Cultural Council records include:
FA427 Asian Cultural Council records, Administrative Files, RG 1
FA1400 Asian Cultural Council records, Conferences, Festivals and Seminars RG 2
FA1402 Asian Cultural Council records, Fellowships and Training Programs, RG 4
FA1403 Asian Cultural Council records, Grants, RG 5
Scope and Contents
Records primarily include corrrespondence, meeting records funding files, select grants, as well documentation for and planning of the Festival of India. Festival of India files can also be found in RG 2 (FA1400).
Related Materials
Records documenting the activities of the Indo‐U.S. Sub‐Commission on Education and Culture are contained in several archival collections at RAC including the Asian Cultural Council, the JDR 3rd Fund and the Asia Society. The Sub‐Commission officially closed its office in July 1996.
- Indo-US Subcommission on Education and Culture, 3
  - General Files, 1
    - Indo-US Subcommission, Report and Recommendations, Action, General (Box 278, Folder 1)
    - Third Meeting of the Indo-US Subcommission on Education and Culture, New Delhi, 1977 May 25-26 (Box 278, Folder 2)
    - Meetings of the Indo-US Subcommission on Education and Culture, 1975-1978 (Box 278, Folder 3)
    - Indo-US Joint Committee on Museums Meeting, New Delhi, 1976 February 25-28 (Box 278, Folder 4)
    - Indo-US Subcommission on Education and Culture, Final Narrative Report for the International Communication Agency (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - Subcommission Meeting, Asia House, NYC, 1976 May 4-5 (Box 279, Folder 1)
    - Full Joint Committee on Museums Meeting, Washington, D. C., 1977 February 27-March 1 (Box 279, Folder 2)
    - American Members Meeting of the Joint Subcommission, 1977 December 9 (Box 279, Folder 3)
    - Fourth Meeting of the Indo-US Subcommission on Education and Culture, 1978 May 15-16 (Box 279, Folder 4)
    - Third Full Meeting of the Joint Museum Committee, New Delhi, 1978 March 2-3 (Box 279, Folder 5)
    - Third Full Meeting of the Joint Museum Committee, New Delhi, 1978 2-3 March (Box 280, Folder 1)
    - Indo-US Subcommission on Education and Culture, Meeting of American Members, Washington, D. C., 1977 December 9 (Box 280, Folder 2)
    - Queens College, NY, Akmal Parwez (Box 280, Folder 3)
    - Society for Asian Music, in Conjunction with Metropolitan (Box 280, Folder 4)
    - Planning, D30, 1983 (Box 280, Folder 5)
    - Mira Nair Project (Box 280, Folder 6)
    - Friends of Festival of India (Box 280, Folder 7)
    - Performing Arts, Festival of India, Travel Programs (Box 280, Folder 8)
    - Performing Arts, Festival of India, Radio Projects (Box 280, Folder 9)
    - Performing Arts, "The Canatic Music Tradition", Sean Barlow (Box 280, Folder 10)
    - Performing Arts, Bala Books, Children's Day India (Box 281, Folder 1)
    - Performing Arts, Media Related Programs, Festival of India (Box 281, Folder 2)
    - Performing Arts, Asia, Stage Center, Muriel Peters, B10 (Box 281, Folder 3)
    - Media Related Programs, Film Festival, Museum of Modern Art, B50, 1986 January-September (Box 281, Folder 4)
    - Media Related Programs, Festival of India, Music, Kichlu, Dixit, etc, 1986 January-September (Box 281, Folder 5)
    - Festival of Modern Arts and Indian Music, Liebl, Maureen, Correspondence (Box 282, Folder 1)
    - Festival of Modern Arts and Indian Music, Correspondence with S. Dillon Ripley (Box 282, Folder 2)
    - Festival of Modern Arts and Indian Music, Festival of India, American Committee, G10, 1984-1985 (Box 282, Folder 3)
    - Festival of Modern Arts and Indian Music, Festival of India, Legal Matters (Box 282, Folder 4)
    - Festival of Modern Arts and Indian Music, Festival of India, Legal Matters (Box 283, Folder 1)
    - Festival of Modern Arts and Indian Music, East-West Fusion Theatre (Box 283, Folder 2)
    - Performing Arts, Antaeus Group, Promotional Film and Radio Series, B20 (Box 283, Folder 3)
    - Legal Matters, Festival of India, Education Committee, G60 (Box 283, Folder 4)
    - Legal Matters, Festival of India, Infringement of Trademark (Box 283, Folder 5)
    - Legal Matters, Festival of India, American Committee, Meeting, in DC, G25, 1984 April 5 (Box 283, Folder 6)
    - Festival of India, American Committee (Box 283, Folder 7)
    - Indian Media Contacts (Box 283, Folder 8)
    - Festival of Indian Poetry (Box 283, Folder 9)
    - Rita Gam (Box 283, Folder 10-11)
    - Rita Gam, Columbia Artists Manag., Music and Dance, 10 City Tour of Festival of India (Box 284, Folder 1)
    - Rita Gam, Goodwin Theatre of Austin Arts Center, "The Little Clay Car", Balwant Gargi (Box 284, Folder 2)
    - Rita Gam, University of Maryland, College Park, "Festival of Music" (Box 284, Folder 3)
    - Rita Gam, Gershwin Theatre of Brooklyn College, "Indrani and Sukanya" (Box 284, Folder 4)
    - Rita Gam, Chandas Academy of Dance, Ritha Devi (Box 284, Folder 5)
    - University of Wisconsin, Madison, Bi-lingual Production Sanskrit (Box 284, Folder 6)
    - Mahabharata, Peter Brook (Box 284, Folder 7)
    - American Members, Sub-Commission, Meeting in NY, 1983 December 5 (Box 284, Folder 8)
    - American Members, Sub-Commission, Meeting, 1982 December 6 (Box 284, Folder 9)
    - American Members, Sub-Commission, Meeting in NY, 1981 December 7 (Box 284, Folder 10)
    - Meeting of American Side of Sub-Commission, Minutes, 1980 November 24 (Box 284, Folder 11)
    - IUSSCEC American Panel meeting, 1980 February 11 (Box 284, Folder 12)
    - Meeting of the American Members of the IUSSCEC, Minutes, 1978 November 17 (Box 284, Folder 13)
    - Sub-Commission, American Panel Meeting, 1977 December 9 (Box 284, Folder 14)
    - American Panel of Sub-Commission Meetings, Joint Sub-Commission Meeting, India, 1984 March 5-6 (Box 285, Folder 1)
    - American Panel of Sub-Commission Meetings, Joint Sub-Commission Meeting, Los Angeles, 1983 April 20-22 (Box 285, Folder 2)
    - American Panel of Sub-Commission Meetings, Joint Sub-Commission Meeting, New Delhi, 1982 February 4-5 (Box 285, Folder 3)
    - American Panel of Sub-Commission Meetings, Joint Sub-Commission Meeting, Philadelphia, 1981 March 26-27 (Box 285, Folder 4)
    - American Panel of Sub-Commission Meetings, Third Joint Sub-Commission Meeting, 1977 May 25-26 (Box 285, Folder 5)
    - Joint Sub-Commission Meetings, Attendance Sheets, 1983-1984 (Box 285, Folder 6)
    - Joint Sub-Commission Meetings, Joint Sub-Commission Meeting, India, 1979 March 19-20 (Box 285, Folder 7)
    - Joint Sub-Commission Meetings, Indo-US Subcommission, Meeting, 1979 February (Box 285, Folder 8)
    - Joint Sub-Commission Meetings, Fourth Joint Sub-Commission Meeting, Binders, 1978 April (Box 286, Folder 1)
    - Joint Sub-Commission Meetings, Full Sub-Commission Meeting, Logistics, 1977 May (Box 286, Folder 2)
    - Joint Sub-Commission Meetings, Sub-Commission, Full Meeting, 1977 (Box 286, Folder 3)
    - Joint Sub-Commission Meetings, Minutes of Sub-Commission Meeting, 1977 May 25-26 (Box 286, Folder 4)
    - Joint Sub-Commission Meetings, Sub-Commission, 2nd Full Meeting, Agenda, 1976 May (Box 286, Folder 5)
    - Joint Sub-Commission Meetings, Second Meeting of the IUSSCEC, NY, Copies, 1976 May 4-5 (Box 286, Folder 6)
    - Joint Sub-Commission Meetings, First Meeting of the IUSSCEC, 1975 February 3-5 (Box 286, Folder 7)
    - Joint Sub-Commission Meetings, Full IUSSCEC Meeting, 1980 April (Box 286, Folder 8)
    - Fourth Joint Sub-Commission Meeting, Minutes, Asia House, NY, 1978 May 15-16 (Box 287, Folder 1)
    - Film and Broadcasting Meeting, American Members, 1984 November 9 (Box 287, Folder 2)
    - Joint Film and Broadcasting Meeting, 1984 April 24-25 (Box 287, Folder 3)
    - Film and Broadcasting Meeting, American Members, NY, 1983 Novmeber 9 (Box 287, Folder 4)
    - Joint Film and Broadcasting Committee, Meeting, New Delhi, 1983 February 17-18 (Box 287, Folder 5)
    - Film and Broadcasting Meeting, 1982 November 10 (Box 287, Folder 6)
    - Joint Film and Broadcasting Meeting, New Delhi, 1982 January 28-29 (Box 287, Folder 7)
    - Film and Broadcasting Committee, Meeting, American Members, NY, 1981 November 11 (Box 287, Folder 8)
    - Joint Film and Broadcasting Committee, Meeting, NY, 1981 June 25-26 (Box 287, Folder 9)
    - Joint Film and Broadcasting Committee, Minutes, New Delhi, 1980 January 18-19 (Box 287, Folder 10)
    - American Side of Film and Broadcasting Committee Meeting, 1980 November 10 (Box 287, Folder 11)
    - Joint Film and Broadcasting Committee, Meeting, Charleston, 1979 February 22-24 (Box 288, Folder 1)
    - Film and Broadcasting Committee, Meeting, 1978 November 9 (Box 288, Folder 2)
    - First Meeting of the Film and Broadcasting Committee, Minutes, New Delhi, 1978 March 10-11 (Box 288, Folder 3)
    - First Joint Film and Broadcasting Meeting, Logistics, New Delhi, 1978 March 10-11 (Box 288, Folder 4)
    - American Members of Museum Committee, Meeting, 1983 November 21 (Box 288, Folder 5)
    - Joint Meeting, Museum Committee, New Delhi, 1983 February 15-16 (Box 288, Folder 6)
    - Museum Committee, Meeting, 1982 November 16 (Box 288, Folder 7)
    - Joint Meeting, Museum Committee, New Delhi, 1982 February 1-2 (Box 288, Folder 8)
    - American Members of Museum Committee, Meeting, NY, 1981 December 4 (Box 289, Folder 1)
    - Joint Meeting, Museum Committee, NY, 1981 March 23-24 (Box 289, Folder 2)
    - Joint Meeting, Museum Committee, 1980 January (Box 289, Folder 3)
    - Museum Committee Meeting, NY, 1979 November 1 (Box 289, Folder 4)
    - Meeting of American Panel, Sub-commission Film and Broadcasting Committee, 1979 November (Box 289, Folder 5)
    - Meeting of the Museum Committee of the IUSSCEC, 1979 February 1-3 (Box 289, Folder 6)
    - Third Meeting of the Joint Museum Committee, Copies, New Delhi, 1978 March 2-3 (Box 289, Folder 7)
    - Minutes of American Meetings, First, Film and Broadcasting, Copies, 1977 December 13 (Box 289, Folder 8)
    - Joint Museum Committee, American Panel Meeting, 1977 December 5 (Box 289, Folder 9)
    - Media Working Group, American Meeting, 1977 December13 (Box 289, Folder 10)
    - Second Meeting of the Joint Museum Committee, Copies, 1977 February 28-March 1 (Box 290, Folder 1)
    - American Panel of Joint Museum Committee, NY, 1976 November 16 (Box 290, Folder 2)
    - American Panel of Joint Museum Committee Meeting, Copies, NY, 1975 September 25 (Box 290, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, A-D, 1981-1987 (Box 290, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, E-H, 1981-1987 (Box 290, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, I-L, 1981-1987 (Box 290, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, M-P, 1981-1987 (Box 290, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence, Q-S, 1981-1987 (Box 290, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence, T-V, 1981-1987 (Box 290, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, W-Z, 1981-1987 (Box 290, Folder 10)
    - Indian Visitors, Under Auspices of Sub-Commission, Not Related to Programs (Box 291, Folder 1)
    - Indian Visitors to US, Requests for Funding (Box 291, Folder 2)
    - Joint SC, Museum, F and B Committee Meeting, Travel, 1982 January-February (Box 291, Folder 3)
    - Ted Tanen, F. A. Long to India, 1981 February (Box 291, Folder 4)
    - Bettye Caldwell, India Trip, 1982 January (Box 291, Folder 5)
    - Travel, M. Leigh, Osterhaus Group, T. Lopes, 1979 November (Box 291, Folder 6)
    - T. Tanen, Trip to India, 1979 (Box 291, Folder 7)
    - Lora Redford and Lydia Gomes Trip to India, 1979 February 10-11 (Box 291, Folder 8)
    - T. Tanen Lion?s Club Award, Newspaper Clippings, 1979 July (Box 291, Folder 9)
    - Ted's Apartment, 1979 (Box 291, Folder 10)
    - Candidates for Secretariat Position (Box 291, Folder 11)
    - Ted Tanen?s Personal File (Box 291, Folder 12)
    - Secretariat, Lora Redford (Box 291, Folder 13)
    - Sub-commission Write-ups (Box 291, Folder 14)
    - Indo-US Subcommission, Calendar of Events, Beginning, 1986 May 1 (Box 291, Folder 15)
    - Sub-Commission, Press Clippings, 1971-1980 (Box 291, Folder 16)
    - Indian Dance (Box 291, Folder 17)
    - Festival of India, England, 1982 (Box 292, Folder 1)
    - Southern Asian Institute, Columbia University (Box 292, Folder 2)
    - Society For South India Studies (Box 292, Folder 3)
    - United States Lumbini Project (Box 292, Folder 4)
    - Study Centers, India, US (Box 292, Folder 5)
    - Trade Wings VIP India Tour, 1987 March (Box 292, Folder 6)
    - Trilateral Commission (Box 292, Folder 7)
    - University of California, Berkeley (Box 292, Folder 8)
    - Wisconsin South Asian Area Center (Box 292, Folder 9)
    - American Institute of Indian Studies (AIIS) (Box 292, Folder 10)
    - Future Projects, Polo Match (Box 292, Folder 11)
    - Arts International (Box 292, Folder 12)
    - The Ashoka Society (Box 292, Folder 13)
    - The Asia Foundation (Box 292, Folder 14)
    - Association for Asian Studies (Box 292, Folder 15)
    - Association of Indians in America, 1976-1980 (Box 292, Folder 16)
    - ASEA, Center for World Music (Box 292, Folder 17)
    - Council on International Exchange of Scholars, 1975 (Box 293, Folder 1)
    - Federation of Indian Association (Box 293, Folder 2)
    - East-West Center (Box 293, Folder 3)
    - Ford Foundation, Grants, General (Box 293, Folder 4)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1977 (Box 293, Folder 5)
    - Foundations, Film, video, etc (Box 293, Folder 6)
    - Fulbright-Hays Program (Box 293, Folder 7)
    - Ford Foundation Round Table, Discussion on India, 1976 April 14 (Box 293, Folder 8)
    - "Indian Shawls and International Significance", The Textile Museum (Box 293, Folder 9)
    - Govinda Gallery (Box 293, Folder 10)
    - University Museum of Architecture/Anthropology, University of Pennsylvania, "Buddhism: History and Diversity of Great Tradition" (Box 293, Folder 11)
    - Clive of India, Royal Oak Foundation (Box 293, Folder 12)
    - "Flowering of the Lotus: Buddhist Art in India", Susan and John Huntington (Box 293, Folder 13)
    - UC Berkeley, University Art Museum, Raghubir Singh Exhibition (Box 293, Folder 14)
    - University of Iowa, Monumental Calligraphy Exhibit (Box 293, Folder 15)
    - Symposium "India 2000: The Next 15 Years", University of Texas, J. Roach, C70 (Box 293, Folder 16)
    - Jawaharlal Nehru, Photographic Exhibit (Box 294, Folder 1)
    - Returns (Box 294, Folder 2)
    - Request for Funding (Box 294, Folder 3)
    - The Canvas of Culture, Rediscovery of the Past as Adaptation for the Future, FOI, Smithsonian Institute (Box 294, Folder 4)
    - "Domestic Painting by Indian Women", Edith Blum Art Institute, Bard College, A30 (Box 294, Folder 5)
    - Princeton University, Conference on Indian Democracy (Box 294, Folder 6)
    - "Contemporary Works on Paper", Milo Beach (Box 294, Folder 7)
    - Newark Museum Exhibition Proposal, A150 (Box 294, Folder 8)
    - Museum Collection of Indian Art (Box 294, Folder 9)
    - University of California, LA, Puppet Exhibition (Box 294, Folder 10)
    - Festival of India (FOI) (Box 294, Folder 11)
    - New York Philharmonic Orchestra, India Tour, Clippings, 1984 (Box 295, Folder 1)
    - Columbia Talk (Box 295, Folder 2)
    - Performing Arts, Potential POI (Box 295, Folder 3)
    - Boston University, Indian Economy: etc (Box 295, Folder 4)
    - Library of Congress: Symposium, "American Understanding of India" (Box 295, Folder 5)
    - The Asia Society, The Immigrant Experience" (Box 295, Folder 6)
    - Forms, INDIA! (Box 295, Folder 7)
    - INDIA!, Write-ups, Originals (Box 295, Folder 8)
    - INDIA! Originals, 1980 February (Box 295, Folder 9)
    - Missoula Museum of the Arts - Women Painters of Mithila (Box 295, Folder 10)
    - INDIA! Publicity (Box 296, Folder 1)
    - INDIA! Funding (Box 296, Folder 2)
    - International Museum of Photography at George Eastman House, "Rosalind Solomon: India" (Box 296, Folder 3)
    - "Elephant Weekend", Bronx Zoo (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - General Conference, FOI, C90 (Box 296, Folder 5)
    - Lamb, Beatrice Pittney - People of India: Living, Working (Box 296, Folder 6)
    - Frederick S. Wright Art Gallery, UCLA - New Tantra Art (Box 296, Folder 7)
    - American Video Festival (Box 296, Folder 8)
    - India Today, General Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 297, Folder 1)
    - India Today, Jazz Yatra (Box 297, Folder 2)
    - INDIA!, Big Blue Marble Filming of Rajeev Sethi?s Crafts Village (Box 297, Folder 3)
    - India Today, Children?s Theatre (Box 297, Folder 4)
    - India Today, Radio (Box 297, Folder 5)
    - American Video Festival in India, 1986 November-December (Box 297, Folder 6)
    - Golden Eye Foundation (Box 297, Folder 7)
    - Indian Business Community (Box 297, Folder 8)
    - India League of America, 1975 (Box 297, Folder 9)
    - JDR 3rd Fund (Box 297, Folder 10)
    - Indo-American Council, Inc. (Box 297, Folder 11)
    - India-US Foundation (Box 297, Folder 12)
    - Institute of International Education, General (Box 297, Folder 13)
    - Meridian House International (Box 297, Folder 14)
    - Overseas Development Council (Box 297, Folder 15)
    - "Outreach Educational Project", Joan Erdman (Box 297, Folder 16)
    - India Arts Publications and Brochures (Box 298, Folder 1)
    - Film India (Box 298, Folder 2-4)
    - Film India, Expenses for MoMA (Box 298, Folder 5)
    - Film India, Part II (Box 299, Folder 1)
    - Film India, Part III, Indian Visitors, Contemporary Indian Cinema (Box 299, Folder 2)
    - Film India, Memos and Faxes (Box 299, Folder 3)
    - Film India, Books (Box 299, Folder 4)
    - Shiva Symposium (Box 299, Folder 5)
    - Film India, Part I, S. Ray, DasGupta, Chandragupta (Box 299, Folder 6)
    - Symposium on Saivism, Philadelphia, 1981 April (Box 299, Folder 7)
    - Asian Cultural Council, Film India Grant (Box 299, Folder 8)
    - Clipping Book (Box 299, Folder 9)
    - INDIA! (Box 299, Folder 10)
    - INDIA! Funding, Air India (Box 299, Folder 11)
    - Manifestations of Shiva (Box 300, Folder 1)
    - Sringar (Box 300, Folder 2)
    - Manifestations of Shiva, Film (Box 300, Folder 3)
    - Other Projects Related to INDIA! (Box 300, Folder 4)
    - India Today, Write-ups (Box 300, Folder 5)
    - India Today, Resumes (Box 300, Folder 6)
    - India Today, California (Box 300, Folder 7)
    - INDIA!, Phoenix (Box 300, Folder 8)
    - India Today, Charleston (Box 300, Folder 9)
    - India Today, Washington, D. C. (Box 300, Folder 10)
    - Philadelphia Museum of Art, Kramrisch (Box 300, Folder 11)
    - Shiva - Loan letters (Box 301, Folder 1)
    - India Today, "Crafts and the Child" (Box 301, Folder 2)
    - ADITI, Fundraising (Box 301, Folder 3)
    - NEH Grant for ADITI, Ref: PM-20129-80-1629 (Box 301, Folder 4)
    - Erdman, Joan, Trip to India, 1980 August (Box 302, Folder 1)
    - ADITI, Catalogue for Exhibit (Box 302, Folder 2)
    - Lowry, Glenn and Michael Brand (Box 302, Folder 3)
    - Festival of India (FOI) - Colloquium of India and US Women Scholars (Box 302, Folder 4)
    - NG of A, Art Institute of Chicago, Harvard, "Indian Sculpture", Chandra, P. (Box 302, Folder 5)
    - University of Minnesota, "Erotic Theme in Indian Cultural Tradition" (Box 302, Folder 6)
    - Seminar on Rural Unemployment, Weisblat, Abraham M., C80 (Box 302, Folder 7)
    - Festival of India (FOI) - Conference, General (Box 302, Folder 8)
    - Patronage in Indian Culture: Religion, Politics, Aesthetics, Miller, Barbara S. (Box 302, Folder 9)
    - American Committee for South Asian Art (ACSAA) (Box 302, Folder 10)
    - Marymount Manhattan College (Shiva: Erotic-Ascetic) (Box 302, Folder 11)
    - AIIS, Conference and Symposia (Box 302, Folder 12)
    - Festival of India (FOI) - Planning (Box 302, Folder 13)
    - Festival Funding - Ford Foundation (Box 302, Folder 14)
    - Festival of India (FOI) - Ford Foundation (Box 302, Folder 15)
    - Wenner-Gren Foundation for Anthropological Research (Box 302, Folder 16)
    - Fundraising, New York State Council for Humanities, F50 (Box 302, Folder 17)
    - Pan Am, Festival Funding, F80 (Box 302, Folder 18)
    - Festival of India - Potential Funding (Box 302, Folder 19)
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, Funding, Budget (Box 303, Folder 1)
    - J. Tandon Association, Funding, F65 (Box 303, Folder 2)
    - 8561, NEA Planning Grant, for FOI (Box 303, Folder 3)
    - Festival of India (FOI) - Contributions - Washington Post (Box 303, Folder 4)
    - Funding, Air India (Box 303, Folder 5)
    - Festival of India (FOI) - Festival Funding - Acknowledgements (Box 303, Folder 6)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, FOI Planning Grant,#42-3052-0022 (Box 303, Folder 7)
    - Festival of India - Dallas-Fort Worth, TX (Box 303, Folder 8)
    - Galleries (Box 303, Folder 9)
    - Festival of India (FOI) - Fundraising (Box 303, Folder 10)
    - Festival of India (FOI) - Hawaii Projects (Box 303, Folder 11)
    - India Today, Dance, Kathakali (Box 303, Folder 12)
    - Original Agreement, 1974 October 23 (Box 304, Folder 1)
    - Asian Cultural Council, Certificate of Incorporation, Board of Trustees, Tax-Exempt Letter, RSL Biography (Box 304, Folder 2)
    - First Meeting, New Delhi, India, 1975 February 3-5 (Box 304, Folder 3)
    - American Panel of SC Meeting, New York, 1975 October 8 (Box 304, Folder 4)
    - 1994 Lease at 280 Madison Avenue (Box 304, Folder 5)
    - Joint Commission Meeting, 1975 October 6-7 (Box 304, Folder 6)
    - Joint Commission Meeting, 1979 April 24 (Box 304, Folder 7)
    - Joint Commission (Box 304, Folder 8)
    - American Members, Sub-commission Meeting, 1984 December 14 (Box 304, Folder 9)
    - Museum Committee, American Members, 1984 November 14 (Box 304, Folder 10)
    - Joint Museum Committee, 1984 April 9-10 (Box 304, Folder 11)